Roni Sarig Collection, 1984-2007, bulk 2000-2007 SC 148
Archives of African American Music and Culture
Roni Sarig Collection
1984-2007
2000-2007
Archives of African American Music and Culture
Sarig, Roni (Writer on music)
SC 148
2 document cases 0.84 linear feet
40 Audiocassettes
12 photographs
approximately 155 negatives
Interviews with key figures in southern hip hop music and related secondary source materials including articles, press clippings, press releases and photographs.
Arrangement
Arranged in two series:
Series 1: Research Materials; orgainzed in sub-series by state
Series 2: Interviews (audio)
Biographical / Historical
Roni Sarig is a New York-based writer primarily known for his coverage of popular music and Jewish culture. A former music editor of the Atlanta alternative weekly, Creative Loafing, he has also written numerous articles about music for Vibe, Rolling Stone, XXL, and Spin magazines and has published two books about music: The Third Coast: Outkast, Timbaland, and How Hip Hop Became a Southern Thing and Secret History of Rock: The Most Influential Bands You've Never Heard.
Access Restrictions
Use of time-based media materials (audio and video) may require production of listening or viewing copies.
Access to streaming audio, moving image, and full resolution digital image materials may currently be restricted to researchers who can authenticate with an IU account or who are physically present on campus. Remote streaming to individual researchers may be allowed with the completion of applicable forms.
For further information about access to online audiovisual materials, contact AAAMC staff at aaamc@indiana.edu.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated to the AAAMC by Roni Sarig in 2010.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of research materials, including press releases, magazine and newspaper clippings, publicity photographs, and interviews related to Roni Sarig's book, Third Coast: OutKast, Timbaland, and How Hip-Hop Became a Southern Thing (Da Capo Press, 2007). The collection documents the emergence of Southern hip hop as a major force in the music industry and the key artists in the states of Texas, Louisiana, Alabama, Mississippi, Georgia, Kentucky, Tennesee, Florida, Virginia and North Carolina.
Rap (Music)--Southern States; Rap musicians--Southern States; Sound recording executives and producers; African American sound recording executives and producers
- 1. Research Materials, 1984-2007; undated; 83 Folders; Includes primarily press releases and press clippings, with some publicity photographs, transcripts, and typed notes. Clippings include articles from Murder Dog, Vibe, Source, XXL, Complex, Billboard, Urb, Fader, Black Beat, Ozone, Next Level, Dub and Xplosive.
  - 1.1. Alabama, 2005-2007; undated; 3 Folders
    - Dirty, 2005; undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Gucci Mane, undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Rich Boy, 2007; undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes 8x10 photograph
      - Rich Boy, 2007; PA012358; 1 Item 1 photograph: b&w; 8 x 10 in. (Box 1)
        Image Collections Online
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000359
        Rap musicians
  - 1.2. Florida, 1985-2006; undated; 13 Folders
    - 2-Live-Crew, 1990-1994; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Blowfly, 1999-2004; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - DJ Khaled, 2006; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - DJ Khaled, undated; PA012370; 1 Item 1 photograph: b&w; 8 x 10 in. (Box 1)
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000371
    - Jacki-O, 2004; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Jacki-O, undated; PA012359; 1 Item 1 photograph: b&w; 8 x 10 in. (Box 1)
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000360
    - Florida research, 1984-2001; undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Partners in Crime, 2005; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Pitbull, 2004-2005; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Pitbull, undated; PA012360; 1 Item 1 photograph: b&w; 8 x 10 in. (Box 1)
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000361
    - Pretty Tony and Trinere, 1985; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Slip-N-Slide, 2005; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Storch, Scott, undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Superiority Complex, undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Trick Daddy, 2001-2002; undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Contents: Includes typed article by Sarig
    - Trina, 2005-2006; undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1.3. Georgia, 1988-2007; undated; 20 Folders
    - Atlanta research, 1988-1992; undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Contents: Jim Crow, Tango Redd, Da Back Wudz, Stat Quo, Bigg Jus, Duice, DJ Mars, L.A. Reid
    - Bone Crusher, 2003; undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Crunk, 2003; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Da Muzicianz (D-Roc, Mr. Ball, Da Birthday Boy), 2006; undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Da Muzicianz, undated; PA012361; 1 Item 1 photograph: b&w; 8 x 10 in. (Box 1)
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000362
    - Dem Franchise Boyz, 2004; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Field Mob, undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Georgia research, 1993-2005; undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 23)
      Contents: Jody Breeze, Dungeon Family, Tag Team, Bubba Sparxxx, D4L, Youngbloodz, Bone Crusher, Pastor Troy, Blount Ave, Empact Strong, Currency Committee, Champ, Chickenlegs,Pimpzilla, Circle Boyz, Yamo, Jason Geter, Slim-Bo, Buckwild Click, Criminal Manne, D-Shot
    - Goodie Mob, 1998-2004; undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Jazze Pha, undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Jermaine Dupri, 1996-2005; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Kilo, 1991; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Lil Jon & The East Side Boyz, 2004-2005; undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Ludacris, 2000-2006; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Mercedes, Tony, 1997; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Outkast, 2001-2005; undated; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Pastor Troy, 2006-2007; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Pastor Troy, undated; PA012362; 1 Item 1 photograph: b&w; 8 x 10 in. (Box 1)
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000363
    - T.I., 2003-2005; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Ying-Yang Twins, 2002-2005; 1 Folder (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - The Ying Yang Twins, undated; PA012363; 1 Item 1 photograph: color; 8 x 10 in. (Box 1)
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000364
    - Young Dro, 2006; undated; 1 Folder (Box 2)
      Includes interview transcript
    - Young Jeezy & Boyz in da Hood, 2007; undated; 1 Folder
  - 1.4. Louisiana, 2002-2007; undated; 17 Folders
    - B.G. (B. Gizzle), 2004-2007; 1 Folder
      Includes 1 8x10 photograph of B.G., and 1 8x10 photograph og B.G. & The Chopper City Boyz
      - B.G. AKA B. Gizzle, undated; PA012364; 1 Item 1 photograph: b&w; 8 x 10 in. (Box 2)
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000365
      - B.G & The Chopper City Boyz, undated; PA012369; 1 Item 1 photograph: b&w; 8 x 10 in. (Box 2)
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000370
    - Beats By the Pound (KLC, aka Craig Stephen Lawson), undated; 1 Folder
    - Big Tymers (Bryan "Baby Williams and Mannie Fresh), 2003-2004; undated; 1 Folder
      Contents: Includes typed notes (possibly a transcript)
    - Birdman, undated; 1 Folder
    - C-Murder, 2005; 1 Folder
    - Cash Money Records, 2004-2005; 1 Folder
    - D-Boyz, 2005; 1 Folder
    - Hip-Hop Response to Katrina, 2005; 1 Folder
    - Juvenile, 2004; 1 Folder
    - Lil Boosie and Webbie, 2004-2005; undated; 1 Folder
    - Lil Wayne, 2002-2005; 1 Folder
    - Mannie Fresh, 2004; 1 Folder
    - Master P (aka Percy "Master P" Miller of No Limit Records), 2005; undated; 1 Folder
    - Soulja Slim, 2005; undated; 1 Folder
    - TRU (Master P & Silkk the Shocker), 2004; 1 Folder
      - TRU, undated; PA012365; 1 Item 1 photograph: b&w; 8 x 10 in. (Box 2)
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000366
    - Turk, undated; 1 Folder
    - Young Bleed, undated; 1 Folder
  - 1.5. Mississippi, 2003-2005; undated; 3 Folders
    - Banner, David, 2003-2005; 1 Folder
    - Mississippi artists, undated; 1 Folder
      Contents: Gator Boyz, C.O. Tha! Bad Black
    - Rainman, undated; 1 Folder
      - Rainman, undated; PA012366; 1 Item 1 photograph: color; 8 x 10 in. (Box 2)
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000367
  - 1.6. Tennessee and Kentucky, 2003-2006; undated; 5 Folders
    - Kapone, Al, undated; 1 Folder
      Includes 5x7 photograph
      - Al Kapone a.k.a. Al Kapeezy, undated; PA012367; 1 Item 1 photograph: b&w; 5 x 7 in. (Box 2)
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000368
    - Memphis artists, 2005; undated; 1 Folder
    - Nappy Roots, undated; 1 Folder
    - Three 6 Mafia, 2003; 1 Folder
    - Yo Gotti, 2004-2006; 1 Folder
  - 1.7. Texas, 2003-2007; undated; 13 Folders
    - Big Mike, 2005; undated; 1 Folder
    - Bun B, 2004-2005; 1 Folder
    - Chamillionaire, 2005; undated; 1 Folder
    - Geto Boys, 2005; 1 Folder
    - J Xavier, 2006; 1 Folder
    - Jokaman, 2005; 1 Folder
    - Jones, Mike, 2004-2005; undated; 1 Folder
    - Lil Flip', 2003-2004; 1 Folder
      Includes typed transcript
    - Texas artists, 2004-2007; undated; 1 Folder
      Contents: E.S.G., Swishahouse, Hustlamade Bugz, Mike Jones, Rydah, Mob Figaz, 8Ball & MJG, Paul Wall, Papa Reu, D.S.R., 3 of a Kind, Dirty South Rydaz, Chingo Bling, Countri Boi.
    - Screwed and Chopped Sound, 2005; undated; 1 Folder
    - Slim Thug & Boss Hogg Outlawz, 2007; undated; 1 Folder
    - Wall, Paul, 2005; undated; 1 Folder
    - Z-Ro, undated; 1 Folder
  - 1.8. Virginia and North Carolina, 2003-2006; undated; 5 Folders
    - Clipse, 2006; 1 Folder
    - Missy Elliott, undated; 1 Folder
    - Pharrell and Neptunes, 2003-2004; undated; 1 Folder
      Includes 8x10 color photograph
      - Pharrell, 2005; PA012368; 1 Item 1 photograph: color; 8 x 10 in. (Box 2)
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000369
    - Timbaland & Magoo, 2005-2006; undated; 1 Folder
    - Virginia and North Carolina artists, 2003-2005; undated; 1 Folder
      Contents: Nottz, D.M.P., Skillz, Little Brother, Brother Reade
  - 1.9. General research, 1998-2006; undated; 4 Folders
    - Dirty South Hip Hop, 2002-2003; 1 Folder
    - Koch Records press releases, various artists, 2006; 1 Folder
    - Sarig research notes, 2005; undated; 1 Folder
    - Photographs: Goody Mobb and Outkast, 1998-1999; 1 Folder
- 2. Interviews (audio), undated; 40 audio recordings
  - 2.1. Interviews conducted by Roni Sarig, undated; 34 Audio Files
    - Interviews with DJ Smurf, DJ Laz, and Pretty Tony, undated; CASS 2171; Sarig, Roni (Writer on music); 1 Audiocassette: digital + 1 index
      Streaming online in Media Collections Online
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k12831ds9q
      Content
      DJ Smurf, DJ Laz, and Pretty Tony Butler interviewed by Roni Sarig, author of the book, The Third Coast: Outkast, Timbaland, and How Hip Hop Became a Southern Thing.
      Sarig and Atlanta artist DJ Smurf (aka Mike Crooms) discuss Smurf's artistic inspiration and collaboration preferences. DJ Smurf then describes the evolution of crunk dance and explains how bass dancing predates crunk. They also talk about the effect of media on form and structure. Florida artist DJ Laz (aka Lazaro Mendez) talks about his childhood and familial life, as well as the music he listened to growing up, the genesis of bass music, his role in the music business, and influential DJ's. Florida producer "Pretty Tony" Butler talks about the beginning his career, his high school technical education, record pools experience and public DJ experience. Roni Sarig and Pretty Tony discuss the beginnings of Tony's music career, the genesis of his DJ moniker, his collaborations with various artists, his start-up studio and future aspirations, and his activities outside of music.
      General
      Preferred Citation: Roni Sarig Collection, SC 148, Archives of African American Music and Culture, Indiana University, Bloomington.
      Venue/Event Date: Date of recording unknown, but likely 2000-2006.
      Rap (Music)--Southern States; Rap musicians--Southern States; African American sound recording executives and producers
    - Interviews with Henry Stone, Gregory D, Disco Rick, and Allen Johnston, undated; CASS 2172; Sarig, Roni (Writer on music); 1 Audiocassette: digital + 1 index
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s55m31301w
      Henry Stone, Gregory D, Disco Rick, and Allen Johnston interviewed by Roni Sarig, author of the book, The Third Coast: Outkast, Timbaland, and How Hip Hop Became a Southern Thing.
      Henry Stone, producer and owner of TK Records in Florida, discusses opening his first record label which at the time was the only labels and distribution company in the area, signing the Gucci Crew, his next label and some more groups he acquired. Disco Rick, an original member of the Gucci Crew, talks about the group's beginnings, how Luke was instrumental in their success, the history and culture of bass music and how it affected the Gucci Crew and other hip hop acts, how Luke's involvement with the law impacted the group, and what happened to the group afterwards. Florida artist Disco Rick talks about the impact of the song "Whoomp!", changes in the style of bass music, moving to Atlanta to produce rap for other artists [concludes abruptly due to tape malfunction]. Allen Johnston discusses growing up in Chicago, moving to Miami and his early involvement in the music scene, the origin of heavy bass music and the artists responsible. Gregory D talks about growing up in New Orleans and his early involvement in music, getting into hip hop in the early 1980s while in high school, the local hip hop scene, how Ninja Crew was signed to 4 Sight Records, and why they don't create bass music.
      Rap (Music)--Southern States; Rap musicians--Southern States; Sound recording executives and producers
    - Interviews with Tony Mercedes, Jimmy Brown, and MC Shy D, undated; CASS 2173; Sarig, Roni (Writer on music); 1 Audiocassette: digital + 1 index
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d37583zz0h
      Atlanta artists and producers Tony Mercedes, Jimmy Brown and MC Shy D interviewed by Roni Sarig, author of the book, The Third Coast: Outkast, Timbaland, and How Hip Hop Became a Southern Thing.
      Sarig and Tony Mercedes discuss the child molestation controversy that involved Diamond; ownership of his records after his distribution label filed for bankruptcy and the financial issues the bankruptcy caused; becoming a director at LaFace Records after leaving So So Def; eventually leaving LaFace to work on his own business; how and when Atlanta became a big name in the music industry and which artists played a role; how Atlanta earned its spot as a hip-hop mecca. Jimmy Brown talks about his early life in Savannah, Georgia, and his introduction to music; joining the military and his involvement with various bands; moving to Atlanta and playing with several bands; Michael Mauldin, his past stage manager; and an in depth discussion about his kids and their talents. MC Shy D explains that he was one of the first rappers in Atlanta; getting a record deal with 4 Sight Records; leaving the label for Luke Skyywalker Records; disputes over royalties; filing a lawsuit against Luke; creating his own music and forming a record label; and the reasons he served time in prison.
    - Interviews with Kawan "KP" Prather and Ryan Cameron, undated; CASS 2174; Sarig, Roni (Writer on music); 1 Audiocassette: digital + 1 index
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/039k129d6d
      Atlanta artists Kawan "KP" Parther and Ryan Cameron interviewed by Roni Sarig, author of the book, The Third Coast: Outkast, Timbaland, and How Hip Hop Became a Southern Thing.
      KP talks about his childhood and some of the issues he faced growing up, the various kids and groups he met and eventually coming together to form the Dungeon Family; how the group P.A. was signed, their first album release, how it affected their mindset going forward; KP's strengths in helping others showcase their talent and forming his own production company; how he met and signed Reese. Ryan Cameron talks about his youth, how he finitially got into music and a few of his favorite local artists at the time; the music convention, Jack The Rapper's Family Affair, and how it helped many artists get discovered; Antonio "LA" Reid and Kenneth "Babyface" Edmonds form LaFace Records, signing their first artist Damian Dame, and the label's influence within Atlanta; his early experience in radio, working at the city's only hip hop station.
    - Interviews with Crunchy Black and DJ Paul, undated; CASS 2175; Sarig, Roni (Writer on music); 1 Audiocassette: digital + 1 index
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/425k323h45
      Crunchy Black and DJ Paul interviewed by Roni Sarig, author of the book, The Third Coast: Outkast, Timbaland, and How Hip Hop Became a Southern Thing.
      Sarig talks with former Three 6 Mafia member Crunchy Black about his childhood in Memphis and early career, his relationships with other Three 6 Mafia members and the possibility for him to record a solo album. Sarig talks with DJ Paul about his early musical background and influences, his relation to Lord Infamous, his experience creating mixtapes, Three 6 Mafia's dark style and where it comes from and how the group got together. Continued on Side B. Sarig and Paul discuss several topics related to Three 6 Mafia and Memphis, including Three 6 Mafia's album "Most Known Unknown," their involvement with the film "Hustle and Flow," as well as the connection between the Memphis sound and crunk music. They also discuss how Memphis artists tend not to work together.
      Rap (Music)--Southern States; Rap musicians--Southern States
    - Interviews with Nick Scarfo, Juicey J, MJG, and Jazze Pha, undated; CASS 2176; Sarig, Roni (Writer on music); 1 Audiocassette: digital + 1 index
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/1687527j83
      Memphis artists Scarfo, Three 6 Mafia's Juicy J, MJG and Jazze Pha interviewed by Roni Sarig, author of the book, The Third Coast: Outkast, Timbaland, and How Hip Hop Became a Southern Thing.
      Sarig and Scarfo discuss his early investment and involvement with Three 6 Mafia, as well as his record label Prophet Posse. Three 6 Mafia's Juicy J talks about his relationship to other Three 6 Mafia members, particularly DJ Paul, as well as their record label, Hypnotize Minds. Sarig and MJG discuss the rap scene in Memphis and MJG and 8Ball's interactions with other artists; MJG's early musical experiences; the duo's experience recording on OTS and Suave House, and their experience recording in Houston. Roni Sarig talks with producer Jazze Pha about his musical experiences growing up, as well as different aspects of his career, including his early records before he was a producer, his collaborations with various groups and artists, and Sho Nuff Records; rhey also talk about the music scenes in both Memphis and Atlanta, and how Atlanta's music has changed over the course of Pha's career.
    - Interviews with J-Dogg and Knottz, undated; CASS 2177; Sarig, Roni (Writer on music); 1 Audiocassette: digital + 1 index
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/425k323h5g
      J-Dogg and Nottz interviewed by Roni Sarig, author of the book, The Third Coast: Outkast, Timbaland, and How Hip Hop Became a Southern Thing.
      J-Dogg, of the Memphis-based Select-O-Hits label, discusses early Memphis artists like 8Ball & MJG, Al Kapone, and Pretty Tony; problems with record labels in Memphis; racial tensions in the city and how it causes some rappers to leave. Norfolk Virginia rapper and producer Nottz (aka Dominick J. Lamb) discusses his early work with rappers Busta Rhymes and Scarface, and the Virginia hip-hop sound. Discussion about the culture of artists in Virginia, lack of collaboration, Nottz's process for producing records and some of his upcoming projects. Sarig and J-Dogg continue their discussion of hip-hop history in Memphis; the two large cliques in Memphis circles, one with DJ Paul, Juicy J, and other members of Three 6 Mafia, and one with DJ Squeeky and others; problems with record labels, including Outlaw, and Select-O-Hits's reluctance to sign gangster rappers.
    - Interviews with Clarence "Blowfly" Reid, David Noller and Charles Young, undated; CASS 2178; Sarig, Roni (Writer on music); 1 Audiocassette: digital + 1 index
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/b88q37ww48
      Clarence "Blowfly" Reid, David Noller and Charles Young interviewed by Roni Sarig, author of the book, The Third Coast: Outkast, Timbaland, and How Hip Hop Became a Southern Thing.
      Clarence begins the interview by talking about meeting and working with various artists. They then discuss the origin of rap and Clarence's place in the new genre. They finish the interview by discussing Luke's success and how it helped Clarence get recognition for the work he has doing for years before the 2 Live Crew came around. Sarig and Noller talk about Norberto and his reputation, including his club Bass Station, crimes and his death. Noller talks about his and Eric's involvement with Suntown Records. He then talks about his original partner before leading to the partner he had when signing to Bass Station. They talk about "Just Give the DJ a Break," and the groundbreaking technology of multi-tuned bass, which was used to make the record, and then they talk about the various dances associated with bass music. Noller finishes the interview by talking about the possible divide between booty music, bass music, and others that were popular at the time. Charles Young talks about his childhood in Miami and meeting several people who went into the DJ scene with him in the 70s. Sarig and Charles discuss Bass Station and Candyman, the owner of the club, before discussing the circumstance revolving around Norberto's death. They discuss "Give Me All You've Got," describing the various issues surrounding the track, the downfall of Suntown, and finish with talking about the origin of booty dancing.
    - Interviews with Magic Mike and Clarence "Blowfly" Reid, undated; CASS 2179; Sarig, Roni (Writer on music); 1 Audiocassette: digital + 1 index
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/049g15ch79
      Magik Mike and Clarence "Blowfly" Reid interviewed by Roni Sarig, author of the book, The Third Coast: Outkast, Timbaland, and How Hip Hop Became a Southern Thing.
      Mike talks about moving to Orlando and getting into playing hip hop and bass music in clubs. Sarig and Mike then talk about the roots of bass music and the various artists that helped define it. They discuss what happened later with various artists, such as Cool Rock & Chaszy Chess and Prince Rakeem before wrapping up with a discussion on car audio. Clarence begins by talking about his childhood in Georgia and some of the songs he would make up. Clarence shares various short stories on topics including how he got his nick name "Blowfly," his school life, family members, meeting famous artists, and experiencing prejudice. Clarence then talks about Henry Stone and the circumstances that led to him recording his own music as Blowfly in 1960. They talk about several of his first records, including The World of Blowfly.
      (Continues on CASS 2178)
    - Interviews with MC Shy-D, Missy Elliott, and Willie D, undated; CASS 2181; Sarig, Roni (Writer on music); 1 Audiocassette: digital + 1 index
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d07g74rr8z